So let's go back to our project
그럼 우리의 프로젝트로 돌아가자
are this task.
I will create a new function.
새로운 기능을 만들겠습니다.
I will create a function by the name of histogram
히스토그램이라는 이름으로 함수를 생성하겠습니다.
so first of all I have to create a dynamic editor to store all the intensity values.
그래서 우선 모든 강도 값을 저장할 동적 편집기를 만들어야 합니다.
So I will create a dynamic at a here we know dynamic areas known as vector.
그래서 저는 여기에서 벡터로 알려진 동적 영역을 생성할 것입니다.
So I will create a vector.
그래서 벡터를 생성하겠습니다.
Next all the values in our vector will be integers so I will define the end.
다음으로 벡터의 모든 값은 정수가 되므로 끝을 정의하겠습니다.
Next I will type the name of the vectors on there see the name of the vector will be his to ground floor
다음으로 나는 거기에 벡터의 이름을 입력할 것이고 벡터의 이름은 1층에 그의 이름이 될 것입니다.
of a plain histogram Lane.
일반 히스토그램 레인의
So I will type the name as histogram Lane.
그래서 이름을 히스토그램 Lane으로 입력하겠습니다.
Next go to your function.
다음으로 기능으로 이동하십시오.
We have defined our vector now in the first step.
이제 첫 번째 단계에서 벡터를 정의했습니다.
We have to adjust the size of our dynamic every means vector so just the name of the vector.
우리는 동적 벡터의 크기를 조정하여 벡터의 이름만 조정해야 합니다.
So this will be histogram lean.
그래서 이것은 히스토그램 린이 될 것입니다.
Now I will g in this size to 400.
이제 이 크기를 400으로 지정하겠습니다.
There will be over width of over frame so we can use histogram Lane dart resize function re size or
히스토그램 레인 다트 크기 조정 기능을 사용할 수 있도록 오버 프레임의 너비가 초과되거나 크기가 조정됩니다.
the width although the frame is 400 in the next time I will it all the values in my histogram so as
다음 번에 프레임이 400이지만 너비는 내 히스토그램의 모든 값을 다음과 같이
to lean forward this I can use a clear cone
이것을 앞으로 기울이기 위해 나는 깨끗한 원뿔을 사용할 수 있습니다
at this point.
If you know the vectors and your basic operations then you can clearly understand what's going on here.
벡터와 기본 작업을 알고 있다면 여기서 무슨 일이 일어나고 있는지 명확하게 이해할 수 있습니다.
But if you do not know about the vectors then you can learn basic vector operations from this website.
그러나 벡터에 대해 모른다면 이 웹사이트에서 기본적인 벡터 연산을 배울 수 있습니다.
I will link this webpage in the resources section so that you can easily learn about the vectors and
이 웹페이지를 리소스 섹션에 연결하여 벡터 및
their basic operations so all the basic vector operation that I will use in my project.
기본 작업이므로 내 프로젝트에서 사용할 모든 기본 벡터 작업입니다.
You can learn from here and most importantly one example also.
여기에서 가장 중요한 한 가지 예도 배울 수 있습니다.
Now let's go back to our project in the next step.
I will create a for loop to process a word strips in our reason of interest.
이제 다음 단계의 프로젝트로 돌아가 보겠습니다.
So for this I will create a for loop
그래서 이것을 위해 for 루프를 만들 것입니다
so in the next step we have to define the word of a frame so a word of over theme is 400 and the next
그래서 다음 단계에서 우리는 프레임의 단어를 정의해야 합니다. 그래서 over theme의 단어는 400이고 다음은
step I will increment this.
단계 나는 이것을 증가시킬 것입니다.
Now anytime if you change the framework in the future then you have to change the value from here also.
이제 미래에 프레임워크를 변경하면 언제든지 여기에서 값을 변경해야 합니다.
But you can avoid this situation by using the frame size signals or type here.
그러나 프레임 크기 신호를 사용하거나 여기에 입력하면 이러한 상황을 피할 수 있습니다.
As frame dart size now this whole command will return the size of the frame so the size of the frame
이제 프레임 다트 크기로 이 전체 명령은 프레임 크기를 반환하므로 프레임 크기가
is 400 multiplied by 250.
400 곱하기 250입니다.
But we only need a word for one frame so we can type a gifted dart width.
그러나 우리는 재능 있는 다트 너비를 입력할 수 있도록 한 프레임에 대한 단어만 필요합니다.
Now this whole condition will return the value of 400.
이제 이 전체 조건은 400 값을 반환합니다.
That is your frame word but for my project I'm not going to change my frameworks so I can simply use
그것은 당신의 프레임 단어이지만 내 프로젝트의 경우 단순히 사용할 수 있도록 프레임 워크를 변경하지 않을 것입니다.
a 400 here
여기 400
for more information.
자세한 내용은.
I can also add a comment his or frame dart size.
나는 또한 주석을 추가하거나 프레임 다트 크기를 추가할 수 있습니다.
This will give us size as 400 by 240 but if you want only what you can type Dart with here now the value
이렇게 하면 크기가 400 x 240으로 표시되지만 여기에서 Dart를 입력할 수 있는 항목만 원하면 이제 값을 입력합니다.
of this will be 400
이것의 400이 될 것입니다
so in the next half I needed a reason of interest in which I would create strips.
그래서 다음 절반에는 스트립을 만들 관심의 이유가 필요했습니다.
So let us define a new variables so this will be reason of interest for our lean.
따라서 이것이 우리의 린(lean)에 대한 관심의 이유가 될 수 있도록 새 변수를 정의하겠습니다.
This is a new Mac variable so we have to define this married variable here.
이것은 새로운 Mac 변수이므로 여기에서 이 결합된 변수를 정의해야 합니다.
Let's say I will start with a new line Maggie.
새 라인 Maggie로 시작한다고 가정해 보겠습니다.
This will be our way lane
이것은 우리의 차선이 될 것입니다
now.
The next step is for which frame I will create a reason often trust.
다음 단계는 내가 자주 신뢰하는 이유를 만들 프레임입니다.
So if I run this program I just want everyday reason of interest for this frame so this image is our
따라서 이 프로그램을 실행하면 이 프레임에 대한 관심의 일상적인 이유가 필요하므로 이 이미지는
final image and the name for our final image is free and painless so I will use it frame final here
최종 이미지와 최종 이미지의 이름은 무료이며 고통이 없으므로 여기에서 최종 이미지 프레임을 사용하겠습니다.
frame.
Final next I will pass a rectangular argument to create a reason of interest.
마지막으로 관심의 이유를 만들기 위해 직사각형 인수를 전달합니다.
Now this parameter is a explained here.
이제 이 매개변수에 대해 설명합니다.
You can see from here of a rectangular function.
여기에서 직사각형 함수를 볼 수 있습니다.
Now the next question is how we can create a script from this rectangular function so I can simply change
이제 다음 질문은 이 직사각형 함수에서 스크립트를 생성하여 간단히 변경할 수 있는 방법입니다.
the word of each trip to 1 instead of 400.
각 여행의 단어는 400 대신 1입니다.
Now this whole command will create a single sip with the words of one but we have to move all these
이제 이 전체 명령은 하나의 단어로 한 모금을 만들지만 이 모든 것을 움직여야 합니다.
steps with the for loop so I can simply pass the integer here.
for 루프로 단계를 수행하여 여기에 정수를 전달할 수 있습니다.
Now in this way we can process our whole reason of interest but in 400 different scripts in the next
이제 이러한 방식으로 관심 이유를 모두 처리할 수 있지만 다음 단계에서는 400개의 다른 스크립트에서
step.
단계
I will try to normalize our pixels so I will divide the maximum possible intensity value to each and
픽셀을 정규화하여 가능한 최대 강도 값을 각각에 나누고
every pixel.
모든 픽셀.
So I will use their divide functions or divide.
그래서 나는 그들의 나누기 기능을 사용하거나 나눌 것입니다.
I just wanted to word with the maximum possible in density so the maximum possible intensity for each
나는 밀도에서 가능한 최대로 표현하고 싶었습니다. 그래서 각각에 대해 가능한 최대 강도
and every pixel will be fifty five.
모든 픽셀은 55가 될 것입니다.
This is the maximum possible intensity.
이것은 가능한 최대 강도입니다.
Next I have to specify the input image so input image is our reason of interest
다음으로 입력 이미지가 관심의 이유가 되도록 입력 이미지를 지정해야 합니다.
next.
I will override this reason of interest with the new image.
이 관심 이유를 새 이미지로 무시하겠습니다.
So our team are way lean in the next step.
그래서 우리 팀은 다음 단계에서 훨씬 느슨합니다.
I will push all the intensity values in our dynamic areas so I created a dynamic area by the name of
동적 영역의 모든 강도 값을 푸시하여 동적 영역을 이라는 이름으로 만들었습니다.
histogram lean.
히스토그램 린.
We can see the situation from here.
우리는 여기에서 상황을 볼 수 있습니다.
I will use this.
Now how you can feel the values in the vector.
이제 벡터의 값을 어떻게 느낄 수 있습니까?
We usually fill the values in the vector from the backside.
우리는 일반적으로 뒷면에서 벡터의 값을 채웁니다.
So I will use the DART push on the school back.
그래서 나는 학교 뒤쪽에 DART 푸시를 사용할 것입니다.
Next I have to specify the data type so all the values are in integer.
다음으로 모든 값이 정수가 되도록 데이터 유형을 지정해야 합니다.
Next I will add all the pixel intensities in a single strip.
다음으로 단일 스트립에 모든 픽셀 강도를 추가합니다.
So I believe the sum and our frame is are lean.
그래서 나는 합계와 우리의 프레임이 희박하다고 생각합니다.
Next step we have to define the color.
다음 단계에서는 색상을 정의해야 합니다.
So we have only one color gender because this is a Gr. Gilliam is so I can define 0 here and last we
이것이 Gr이기 때문에 우리는 단 하나의 색 성별만 가지고 있습니다. Gilliam은 여기에서 0을 정의할 수 있습니다.
will close all the round records.
모든 라운드 기록을 닫습니다.
Next is semicolons so we are done with other steps.
다음은 세미콜론이므로 다른 단계를 완료합니다.
I know this part may be complicated for some of you guys but if you still have any questions related
이 부분이 여러분 중 일부에게는 복잡할 수 있다는 것을 알고 있지만 여전히 관련 질문이 있는 경우
to this histogram function then feel free to ask me.
이 히스토그램 기능을 사용하려면 언제든지 저에게 물어보십시오.
So in the next hour we will find the actual position off of billions from this dynamic.
따라서 다음 시간에 우리는 이 역학에서 수십억의 실제 위치를 찾을 것입니다.
Eddie.